Finding aid for the Henry Clay Frick Papers, Series II: Correspondence, 1882-1929, undated HCFF.1.2
The Frick Collection/Frick Art Reference Library Archives
- Hays - Heath (Box 40, Folder 7)
  Heath, D.C., 1898
  Heath, Frances A., 1900
  Heath, W.H., 1907
- Hebert - Hedley (Box 40, Folder 8)
  Hebert, Victor E., 1899-1909
  Heckert, Charles G., 1903
  Heckman, Charles, 1902
  Hedley Gold Mining Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1910-1923
- Heffleman - Henninges (Box 40, Folder 9)
  Heffleman, Dorr, 1916
  Hegeman, Miss, 1914
  Heil, L.N., 1900
  Heine, Paul, 1910
  Heiningen-Neudenau, Grafin zu, 1915
  Heinz, Henry J., 1901-1904[?]
  Heinz, Howard, 1913
  Helen, Countess of Valarez, 1909
  Helena, Tupelo and Decatur Railroad Co. (Tupelo, Miss.), 1901
  Hellen, Jos., 1906
  Hellen, S.J., 1891
  Helman-Taylor Co. (Cleveland, Ohio), 1900
  Helme, Birch, 1922
  Hemphill, Alexander J., 1919
  Henderson, H.M., 1906
  Henning, J.W., 1908-1919
  Henninges, Wm. H., 1910
- Henry - Henschel (Box 40, Folder 10)
  Henry A. Weaver and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1897, undated
  Henry C. Frick Educational Commission (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1920-1925
  Henry D. Winans and May (New York, N.Y.), 1902-1912
  Henry M. Robinson and Co. (Boston, Mass.), 1912
  Henry, Mellinger E., 1913
  Henry Schultheis Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1915
  Henry Shenk Co. [no place], 1912
  Henry Sproul and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1891-1903
  Henry Street Settlement [no place], 1913
  Henry's Lake Club [no place], 1902
  Henschel, C.R., 1912
- Hensel - Hewitt (Box 41, Folder 1)
  Hensel, Bruckmann and Lorbacher (New York, N.Y.), 1898-1903
  Hepburn, Beulah E., 1914
  Herington, C.F., 1915
  Herrick, Asbury Haven, 1908
  Herrick, Myron T., undated
  Herring-Hall-Marvin Safe Co. (Hamilton, Ohio), 1902, undated
  Herring, John A., Mrs., 1896
  Herrlich, John F., 1918
  Herron, Andrew W., 1900
  Herron, John W., 1916
  Herschel, Clemens, 1901
  Hertzog, S.J., 1898
  Hess, A.P., 1918
  Hess, G.E., 1914
  Hesse, G. Emil, 1915
  Hewitt, C. Tefft, 1909
  Hewitt, Dexter W., 1918
- Heyl - Hicks (Box 41, Folder 2)
  Heyl and Patterson, Inc. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1925
  Heywood, F.E.H., 1921
  Heywood, Hermes S., 1907
  Hibben, John Grier, 1914-1917
  Hickock, Paul R., 1916
  Hickok, Ralph K., 1906
  Hickox, Ralph W., 1902, 1905
  Hicks, D.J., 1910
  Hicks, J.E., 1900
  Hicks, R.W., 1901-1909
  Hicks, S.H., 1901
- Higbee - Hill (Box 41, Folder 3)
  Higbee, Geo. H., 1893
  Higginson, H.L., 1911, 1915
  Hight, F.S., 1904
  Hiland Automobile Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1911
  Hilands, Wm. A., 1900
  Hill, Arthur, 1899-1903
  Hill, David Jayne, 1916
  Hill, Hiram, 1904
  Hill, J.M., 1903
  Hill, James J., 1898-1902
  Hill, James J., Mrs., 1916
  Hill, John W., 1904
  Hill, John Wesley, 1913
  Hill, William B., Jr., 1919
- Hilleary - Hinkle (Box 41, Folder 4)
  Hilleary, C.L., 1904
  Hilles, Charles D., 1912
  Hind, C. Lewis, 1919
  Hine, F.L., 1917
  Hines, Alice Macfarlane (Mrs. Walker D. Hines), 1918
  Hines, Walker D., 1910-1919
  Hinguin[?], E.J.V., 1906
  Hinkle, Beatrice M., 1906-1907
- Hinkley - Hitchman (Box 41, Folder 5)
  Hinkley, Harry L., 1923
  Hirsch, I.E., 1899
  Hiscock, Irving D., 1897-1898
  Hiss and Weeks (New York, N.Y.), 1899
  Hiss, Philip, 1896-1903
  Histed, [F.W.], 1904
  Historical Society of Pennsylvania (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1912, 1914
  Hitchings, Hector M., 1919
  Hitchman, W.J., 1881-1894
- Hoadley - Hoes (Box 41, Folder 6)
  Hoadley, Jos. H., 1903
  Hobby, Theodore Y., 1915
  Hodge, S.H., 1913
  Hodges, A.B.W., 1911
  Hodges, Amory G., 1911, 1913
  Hodges, George, 1897-1909, undated
  Hodges, H.F., 1903
  Hodgkins, E., 1910, 1916
  Hoes, William M., 1891
- Hoffman, J. Ogden, 1890-1898 (Box 41, Folder 7-8)
- Hoggson - Holden (Box 41, Folder 9)
  Hoggson, Noble Foster, 1915
  Holbrook, E., 1899, 1917
  Holden, Joshua B., 1915
  Holden, Louis Edward, 1899-1911
- Holland - Holman (Box 41, Folder 10)
  Holland, J.A., 1905
  Holland, J.W., 1916
  Holland, William J., 1901-1919
  Holland House (New York, N.Y.), 1897-1901
  Hollar Lock Inspection and Guaranty Co. of New York (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1902-1905
  Hollar, Wm. H., 1913
  Hollender and Cremeti (London, England), 1896
  Holliday George L., 1906
  Holliday, John, Mrs., 1916
  Denniston, Jas., 1890-1891
  Hollins, H.B., 1908-1913
  Hollis, Wm. H., 1889
  Holloway, A.F., 1915
  Holman, Louis A., 1909
- Holmes, A.G. - Holmes, Wm. N. (Box 41, Folder 11)
  Holmes, A.G., 1916
  Holmes and Campbell's Nut Lock (Alma, Col.), 1898
  Holmes, John G., 1898-1904
  Holmes, O.W., 1895
  Holmes, Samuel, 1901
  Holmes, Sue E. (Mrs. John G. Holmes), 1906-1913, undated
  Holmes, Wm. N., 1902
- Holroyd, John, 1917-1923 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Holroyd, Joseph, 1902-1917 (Box 42, Folder 2-5)
- Holroyd, May - Hooker (Box 42, Folder 6)
  Holroyd, May, 1913-1916
  Holston National Bank of Knoxville (Knoxville, Tenn.), 1905
  Holt, Winifred, 1906, 1910
  Holton, Laura, undated
  Holy Family Orphan Asylum (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1910
  Homœopathic Medical and Surgical Hospital and Dispensary (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1888-1911
  Homer, E.A., 1911
  Homestead (Pa.), Borough of, 1914-1920
  Homestead Business Men's Association (Homestead, Pa.), 1906
  Homestead Hospital Board (Homestead, Pa.), 1908-1911
  Homewood Avenue M.E. Church (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1916
  Homewood Cemetery (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1905, 1909
  Homewood Realty Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1909
  Hook-Hastings Co. (Kendal Green, Mass.), 1905
  Hooker, Howard M., 1910
  Hooker, Susie M., 1904
- Hooper - Hoskies (Box 42, Folder 7)
  Hooper, Franklin W., 1905
  Hoopes, Edward C., 1915
  Hoover, Herbert C., 1917
  Hoover, W.E., 1907
  Hopkins, J. Barry, 1916
  Hopwood, R.F., 1917
  Horace S. Ely and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1909
  Hörmann, Schütte and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1904
  Hornaday, William T., 1901-1913
  Hornberger, J.B.L., 1902, 1909
  Horne, Durbin, 1897, 1906
  Horner and Ladley (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901
  Horner, E.W., 1902
  Horner, Geo. W., 1894
  Horrul, John D., 1912
  Horsfall, James, 1915
  Horton, A. Llewellyn, Mrs., 1914
  Hosack, Geo. M., 1905
  Hoskies, H.C., 1907
- Hosler - Hotchkiss (Box 42, Folder 8)
  Hosler, C.H., 1898
  Hospital Saturday and Sunday Association (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900
  Hospital-School for Backward Children (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1912
  Hossman, [?] (c/o Pullman Company, New York, N.Y.), 1909
  Host, Zeno M., 1905
  Hostetter, D. Herbert, 1915
  Hostetter Connellsville Coke Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1893
  Hotchkin and Co. (Boston, Mass.), 1913
  Hotchkiss, C.W., 1901-1913
  Hotchkiss, Thomas W., 1907
- Hotel Biltmore - Hotel Washington (Box 42, Folder 9)
  Hotel Biltmore (New York, N.Y.), 1920-1924
  Hotel Burlington (Washington, D.C.), 192[?]
  Hotel Manhattan (New York, N.Y.), 1917-1920
  Hotel Touraine (Boston, Mass.), 1918
  Hotel Traymore (Atlantic City, N.J.), 1900
  Hotel Washington (Washington, D.C.), 1921
- Houghton - Hovey (Box 42, Folder 10)
  Houghton, Geo. S., 1908
  Houghton, Mifflin and Co. (Boston, Mass.), 1905
  House, Edward M., 1913-1919
  House of the Good Shepherd (Baltimore, Md.), 1887
  Housman, A.A., 1904
  Housman, Clarence J., 1913
  Houtchens, T.E., 1906
  Hovey, George Rice, 1912
- Howard - Howell, George (Box 42, Folder 11)
  Howard, Francis, 1914
  Howard, M.[?] W. [executor for the estate of Martha H. Childs, Sr.], 1889
  Howard, Oliver Otis, 1909
  Howard, Shafter, 1908
  Howe, A.H., 1908
  Howe, J. Murray, 1908
  Howe, S.O., 1903, 1906
  Howell and Reppert (Uniontown, Pa.), 1890-1894
  Howell, Charles S., 1909
  Howell, George D., 1898-1904
- Howell, Mary - Hoyt (Box 42, Folder 12)
  Howell, Mary, 1915-1916
  Howes, Geo. E., Jr., 1899
  Hoy, Thomas, 1915
  Hoyt, Dustin and Kelley (Cleveland, Ohio), 1900-1906
  Hoyt, Colgate, 1906
  Hoyt, James H., 1892, 1906
- Hubbard - Hugus (Box 43, Folder 1)
  Hubbard, Samuel C., 1901
  Hubbard, Thos. H., 1903
  Hubbs, U.B., 1902
  Hudson, A. Elysabeth, no year
  Hudson, Charles I., 1899-1904
  Hudson, Thos. J., 1898-1901
  Hudson-Fulton Celebration Commission Committee on Art Exhibits [New York, N.Y.], 1909
  Hudson Motor Car Company of N.Y. (New York, N.Y.), 1915
  Huff, Geo. F., 1904
  Huggins, R.R., 1922
  Hughes and Müller (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1900
  Hughes, Elizabeth K. (Mrs. W.E. Hughes), 1911
  Hughes J.L., 1896
  Hughes, Martha C., 1908
  Hughes, Rose Cardwell, 1915
  Hughes, Thos. H., 1898
  Hugus, Elizabeth, 1899
  Hugus, G.D., 1890
- Hughitt, Marvin, 1902-1919 (Box 43, Folder 2-3)
- Huhn, Edey and Co. - Huhn, George (Box 43, Folder 4)
  Huhn, Edey and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1911
  Huhn, George A., 1903-1915
- Huidekoper - Hunnewell (Box 43, Folder 5)
  Huidekoper, A.C., 1896-1901
  Hulings, Willis J., 1915
  Hull, F.A., 1896
  Hull, Geo. H., 1888-1901
  Humffreys-Roberts, R., 1897
  Humphries, E.A., 1889-1896
  Humphrey, Andrew B., 1913
  Humphrey, Marie B. Ives (Mrs. Wm. Brewster Humphrey), 1909
  Humphreys, Alex C., 1915
  Humphries Miller (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1898, 1901
  Hungarian Consul [no place], 1907
  Hunnewell, Henry S., 1917
- Hunsiker, Millard, 1894-1917 (Box 43, Folder 6-9)
- Hunt - Hutchins (Box 43, Folder 10)
  Hunt, Alfred E., 1896
  Hunt and Hunt (New York, N.Y.), 1905-1911
  Hunt, Wm. P., 1904
  Hunter, A.S., 1907
  Hunter, Clara L., 1906
  Hunter, George Leland, 1913
  Hunter, J.G., 1896
  Hunter, Jesse, 1891
  Huntington, Archer M., 1911, 1915
  Huntington, C.P., 1900
  Hurlbut Undertaking and Embalming Co. (Joplin, Miss.), 1909
  Huron College [no place], 1911
  Hussey, John U., 1903
  Huston, Jas. A., 1902
  Hutchings, Geo. S., 1892
  Hutchins, Charles H., 1902
  Hutchins, James C., 1889-1890
- Hutchinson - Hybart (Box 43, Folder 11)
  Hutchinson, A.A., 1917
  Hutchinson, Alexander, 1897
  Hutchinson, Elijah, 1891
  Hutchinson, Henry A., 1903
  Hutchinson, Jesse M., 1919
  Hybart, Annie S., 1914
- Hyde, James H., 1900-1902 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Hyde, James H. (continued), 1903-1905 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Hygeia - Imperial (Box 44, Folder 2)
  Hygeia Ice Company (New York, N.Y.), 1922
  Hylan, [John F.], 1918
  I.P. Frink (New York, N.Y.), 1898
  Ichenhäuser, Julius D., 1907
  Ikirt, Geo. P., 1901
  Illinois Central Railroad Company (New York, N.Y.), 1901-1902
  Illinois Steel Co. (Chicago, Ill.), 1889-1906
  Imel, Judson, Mrs., 1911
  Imgard, Alice F., 1906
  "Immortality" [poem by Joseph Jefferson], 1917
  Imperial German Consul (A. Mezger) [no place], 1916
- Independence - Ingersoll (Box 44, Folder 3)
  Independence League [no place], 1919
  Index Publishing Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1912-1917
  Indian Ridge Coal and Coke Co. [no place], 1906, 1914
  Indiana Harbor (Ind.), 1912
  Industrial Record (Birmingham, Ala.), 1917
  Industrial School for Cripples and Deformed Children (Boston, Mass.), 1906, 1909
  Infants Hospital (Boston, Mass.), 1911-1912
  Ingalls, Melville E., 1905
  Ingersoll, Charles E., 1907-1914
- Inglis - International Banking (Box 44, Folder 4)
  Inglis, James S., 1897-1906
  Inglis, Louise, 1912-1914
  Ingraham, A.J., 1898-1909
  Ingraham, L.S., 1910
  Ingraham, Phoenix, 1919
  Institute Français [no place], 1917
  Inland Steel Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1907, 1909
  Institute of Industrial Research (Washington, D.C.), 1911
  Interborough Rapid Transit Company (New York, N.Y.), 1923
  International Banking Corporation (New York, N.Y.), 1902-1903, 1921
- International Children's School - Izenour (Box 44, Folder 5)
  International Children's School Farm League (New York, N.Y.), 1908
  International Corporate Guarantors Company (New York, N.Y.), 1906
  International Harvester Co. (Chicago, Ill.), 1902
  International Historical Society (New York, N.Y.), 1918
  International League of Press Clubs (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1904
  International News Service (New York, N.Y.), 1915
  International Peace Forum [no place], 1913
  Interstate Coal Company (Columbus, Ohio), 1915
  Interstate Commerce Commission (Washington, D.C.), 1906
  Irish, Howard, 1915
  Irish American Volunteers of the State of New York, 1914
  Iron Age(New York, N.Y.), 1890-1914
  Iron City Engineering Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1916
  Irving, A. Macrobert, 1917
  Irving, E.B., 1908
  Irwin, F.J., 1902
  Isaacs, Albert C., 1900, 1906
  Ivory, Robert B., 1903
  Izenour, Harry F., 1905
- J.A. Strickler Coke Co. - J.E. Caldwell Co. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  J.A. Strickler Coke Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900
  J. and H. Phillips (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1903
  J. and S. Ferguson (New York, N.Y.), 1886-1905
  J.B. Crooks and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1899, 1901
  J.B. Farnham and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1917
  J.C. Cording and Co. (London, England), 1902
  J.C. Kurtz and Son (Chicago, Ill.), 1896
  J.E. Barr and Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1906
  J.E. Caldwell and Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1892-1893
- J. Jacobs and Co. - J.N. Knight and Son (Box 44, Folder 7)
  J. Jacobs and Co. (San Francisco, Cal.), 1889
  J.K. Rice, Jr. and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1910, 1914
  J.L.D. Speer and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1898
  J.M. Askin and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1918
  J.N. Knight and Son (New York, N.Y.), 1915
- J.P. Morgan and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1901-1916 (Box 44, Folder 8-10)
- J. Pearson and Co. - Jackson, Mary (Box 44, Folder 11)
  J. Pearson and Co. (London, England), 1908
  J.S. Bache and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1918
  J.T. Wilson and Son (Nahant, Mass.), 1908-1916
  J.W. Greene, Inc. (Jersey City, N.J.), 1919
  J.W. Hampton, Jr. and Co. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1887, 1899
  Jaccaci, August F., 1913
  Jackman, Edwin S., 1898, 1903
  Jackson, A.F., 1913
  Jackson, Charles C., 1906
  Jackson, Harry B., 1915
  Jackson, John B., 1891-1906
  Jackson, Mary L., 1916
- Jackson, P.C. - James Carothers and Co. (Box 44, Folder 12)
  Jackson, P.C., 1906
  Jacobs, Chas. M., 1889
  Jacobs, Helen P., 1916
  Jacobs, Henry Barton, 1916
  Jacobs, Nannie, 1902
  Jacoby, A.B., 1900
  James, George Abbot, 1911
  James, J.W.H., 1899
  James Carothers and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1903
- James D. Smith and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1895-1900 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- James D. Smith and Co. (continued), 1901-1909 (Box 45, Folder 1-11)
- James D. Smith and Co. (continued), 1909-1914 (Box 46, Folder 1-10)
- James McCutcheon and Co. - Jefferson (Box 46, Folder 11)
  James McCutcheon and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1903, 1906
  James T. White and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1893-1903
  James W. Arrott, Ltd. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1923
  James W. Bell Son and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1903
  Jamieson, Arthur, 1915
  Jamieson, J.C., 1909
  Jamison, John, 1909
  Jansen and Abbott (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1908
  Japan Society of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1910
  Japanese Government, Special Finance Commission (Tokyo, Japan), 1918
  Jaques, William H., 1896, 1900
  Jarrett, John, 1890-1908
  Jarvis, J.N., 1890
  Jarvis, Jos. W., 1905
  Jarvis, Robert R., 1914
  Jas. J. Flannery and Bro. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901
  Jas. P. Donovan and Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901
  Jax Realty and Exchange Company (Jacksonville, Fla.), 1904
  Jefferson, J., 1904
  Jefferson, Joseph, "Immortality" [poem], 1917
  Jefferson, William Winter, 1917
- Jefferys, E.G., 1908 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Jeillaud - Joffre (Box 47, Folder 2)
  Jeillaud, L.C., 1917
  Jekyl Island Club [no place], undated
  Jemison, Robert, Jr., 1917-1919
  Jenkins, A.E., 1898
  Jenkins, G.W., 1900
  Jenkins, Thomas M., 1909
  Jenkinson, A.M., 1901
  Jenkinson, Alex M., 1903
  Jennewine, Chas., 1900
  Jennings, Benj. T., 1902
  Jennings, M.C., 1918
  Jerom, Joseph, 1922
  Jewell, Edward, 1907
  Jewell, Lawrence, 1905
  Jewett, Geo. F., 1896
  Jewett, J.B., 1892
  Jno. A. Williar Co., Inc. (Baltimore, Md.), 1914
  Jno. Hy. Andrew and Co. (Sheffield, [?]),1903
  Joffre, J[oseph-Jacques-Césair], 1917, 1919
- John B. Shannon Co. - Johnson, D.B. (Box 47, Folder 3)
  John B. Shannon Co. [no place], 1915
  John Bradley Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1899
  John C. Yorston and Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1898
  John Curtin, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1908
  John Dewar and Sons, Ltd. (Perth, Scotland), 1897-1902
  John E. Born and Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1921
  John K, Ewing and Co. (Wilkinsburg, Pa.), 1901
  John M. Watson and Co. (New Castle, Pa.), 1889
  Johns, David, 1909
  Johnson, Albert D., 1918
  Johnson, Ann E., [1889?]-1891
  Johnson, Bessie D., 1906
  Johnson, D.B., 1909
  Johnson-Dorrington Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1916
- Johnson, F.W. - Johnson, Katherine (Box 47, Folder 4)
  Johnson, F.W., no year
  Johnson, Guy R., 1897
  Johnson, H.M., 1889
  Johnson, J. Bailey, 1911
  Johnson, Margaret Walker (Mrs. J. Massie Johnson), 1914
  Johnson, John G., 1900-1915, undated
  Johnson, John O., 1904, 1908
  Johnson, Katherine, 1909
- Johnson, L.E., 1906-1920 (Box 47, Folder 5-11)
- Johnson, Mary - Johnston, Charles (Box 47, Folder 12)
  Johnson, Mary Stockly (Mrs. Owen Johnson), 1909
  Johnson, Owen, 1909
  Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1898-1916
  Johnson Service Company (New York, N.Y.), 1913, 1915
  Johnson, Stewart, 1913
  Johnson, W.E., 1917
  Johnson, W.S., 1891
  Johnson, Walter A., 1910, 1919
  Johnston, Charles Marshall, 1907
- Johnston, E.M., Mrs. - Joliet (Box 48, Folder 1)
  Johnston, E.M., Mrs., 1911
  Johnston, F.E., 1905
  Johnston, Fred, 1907
  Johnston, George, 1890
  Johnson, Isabel McE[?],1910
  Johnston, John A., 1907
  Johnston, R.W., 1906
  Johnston, Raoul, 1906
  Johnston, Wm. A., 1903
  Johnstone, F.E., 1910
  Johnstone, Hugo R., 1909
  Joies, Ernest, 1902
  Joliet Steel Company (New York, N.Y.), 1887-1889
- Jones, A.L. - Jones, Wallace (Box 48, Folder 2)
  Jones, A.L., 1916
  Jones, Alfred E., 1905
  Jones and Brindisi [New York, N.Y.], 1921
  Jones and Laughlin Steel Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1903
  Jones, B.F., Jr., 1903-1904
  Jones, Carrie S., 1915
  Jones, E. Alfred, 1911
  Jones, H. Willis, 1900-1915
  Jones, J. Will, 1900
  Jones, John, 1910
  Jones, John D., 1909
  Jones, John J., 1909
  Jones, L.C., 1890
  Jones, Mary Cadwalader, 1916
  Jones, Morgan, 1899
  Jones, Robert Holcombe, 1921
  Jones, S. Moorewood, Mrs., 1919
  Jones, W.H., 1907
  Jones, W.R., 1887
  Jones, Wallace, 1901
- Jongers - Joy (Box 48, Folder 3)
  Jongers, Alphonse, 1910, 1915
  Joplin, Geo. A., 1901
  Jordan, Edward A., 1893
  Jordan, Henry, 1890-1898
  Jordan, James F., 1916
  Jordan, T.D., 1902
  Jordan, W.M., 1897
  Jordan, William George, 1913, 1916
  Jordan, Wm., 1898
  Joseph Horne Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1903-1907
  Joseph Kramer Iron and Steel Co. (Chicago, Ill.), 1901
  Joseph Woodwell Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1904
  Joy, Frank, 1906
- Joyce, Wm. H., 1887-1898 (Box 48, Folder 4-5)
- Joyner - Kahn (Box 48, Folder 6)
  Joyner, Sterling W., 1917
  Juniata College (Huntingdon, Pa.), 1906
  Jusserand, [Jules], 1918
  Just, John A., 1896
  Justice, Jacob, 1886-1897
  Juvenile Court of Allegheny County (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1913
  Kaan, Frank W., 1916
  Kahn, Lazard, 1897, 1902
  Kahn, Otto H., 1902-1919
- Kanawha - Kay (Box 48, Folder 7)
  Kanawha and Hocking Coal and Coke Company (Cleveland, Ohio), 1920
  Kane and Co. (Paris, France), 1901
  Kane, James R., 1903
  Kane, Joseph C., 1897
  Kane, William S., 1897
  Kappeler, E.R., 1899
  Karcher, George H., 1908
  Karslake and Co. (London, England), 1902
  Kaufer, John C., 1914
  Kaukasieli, D.A., 1916
  Kay, James I., 1904-1916
  Kay, James I., Mrs., [1905?], 1913
  Kay, Jenny M., 1904-1919
- Kean - Kelsey (Box 48, Folder 8)
  Kean, Van Cortlandt and Co. (New York, N.Y.), 1904-1905
  Kearney, J.L., 1909
  Keating, A.F., 1896
  Keating, Emily Alice, 1913
  Keck, M.J., 1890
  Keefe, J.S., 1902
  Keefer, Joseph S., 1899
  Keenan, T.J., 1904
  Keep, C.H., 1908
  Keim, M.W., 1886
  Keiser, H.B.A., 1897
  Keister, Lawrence, 1906, 1909
  Keller, Helen, 1911, 1918
  Keller, Philip, Jr., 1900-1908
  Kelley, C.E., 1894
  Kelley, James M., 1921
  Kelley, S.C., 1889
  Kellogg, Beckwith and Emery (New York, N.Y.), 1909
  Kelly, A.J., Jr., 1902-1910
  Kelly, C., Mrs., 1918
  Kelly, Anna K., 1921
  Kelly, E.W., 1914
  Kelly, J.G., 1906
  Kelly, W.F., 1914
  Kelsey, Fred'k. W., 1904
- Kempson - Kennedy, O.W. (Box 48, Folder 9)
  Kempson, St. George, 1902
  Kendall Gold Mining Co. (Spokane, Wa.), 1902-1910
  Kendall, Robert A., 1915
  Kendrick, J.W., 1906
  Kennecott Copper [no place], 1920
  Kennedy, D.J., 1899
  Kennedy, John McCartney, 1917
  Kennedy, John Stewart, 1909
  Kennedy, Julian, 1904, 1909
  Kennedy, Margaret E. (Mrs. William L. Kennedy), 1915
  Kennedy, Moorhead C., 1912-1913
  Kennedy, O.W., 1891-1900
- Kennedy, R.P. - Keresey (Box 48, Folder 10)
  Kennedy, R.P., 1898
  Kennedy, Reid, 1898-1899
  Kennedy, Robt. F., 1897
  Kennedy, Robert Joseph, 1912
  Kennedy, Thos. F., 1915
  Kennedy, W.M., 1904-1908
  Kentland Coal and Coke Company [no place], 1915
  Kerbey, Joseph Orton, 1901, 1904, no year
  Kerby, Frederick M., 1910
  Keresey, George F., 1917-1918
  Keresey, James F., 1916
  Keresey, John T., 1906-1919
- Kerns - Kimbrough (Box 48, Folder 11)
  Kerns, Milton, 1917
  Kerr and Fox (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1901-1904
  Kerr, Howard L., 1904
  Kerr, T.R., 1899
  Kerrigan, L.A., 1903
  Kessler, Cora Parsons (Mrs. George A. Kessler), 1916
  Kessler, George A., 1915-1916
  Keyes, W.E., 1902
  Keyser Bros. and Co. (Baltimore, Md.), 1890
  Keyser, R. Brent, 1890
  Keystone Paving Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900
  Keystone Stable and Storage Co. (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1902
  Kiernan, E.E., 1898, 1901
  Kilgore, E.M., 1913
  Kilhan, A.E., 1912
  Killikelly, Sarah H., 1898
  Kilpatrick, Worth, 1909
  Kimball, B.A., 1918
  Kimball, F.J., 1902
  Kimberly, P.L., 189[?], 1901
  Kimbrough, D.A., 1905
- Kinch, D.B., 1904-1920 (Box 49, Folder 1-8)
- Kindl - King, Moses (Box 49, Folder 9)
  Kindl and Glafey (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1904
  Kindl, F.H., 1899-1909
  Kindred, C.F., no year
  Kineman, R.F., 1912
  King, Byron W., 1898-1899
  King, David Bennett, 1896-1915
  King, Elizabeth S., 1890
  King, George D., 1909-1910
  King, H.G., 1912
  King, Henry H., 1908
  King, Joseph, 1887-1889
  King, M.A., 1898
  King, Moses, 1890-1901
- King, Thos. - Kirkman (Box 49, Folder 10)
  King, Thos. M., 1886-1909
  Kingsley House Association (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1900-1913
  Kinnaird, Emily, 1907
  Kinnear, J.W., 1906
  Kinnicutt, Elenora (Mrs. Francis P. Kinnicutt), 1907
  Kinsman, Chas. F., 1901
  Kinsolving, Arthur B., 1916
  Kirby, Katherine, 1902
  Kirk, Ella B., 1906
  Kirk, S.E., Mrs., 1903
  Kirkman, J.B., 1909
- Kirkwood - Klipstein (Box 49, Folder 11)
  Kirkwood, John M., 1902-1907
  Kiser, C.W., 1908
  Kithil, Karl L., 1910
  Kittanning Public Schools (Kittanning, Pa.), 1916
  Klages, Henry S., 1897
  Kleber, Oscar, Mrs., 1899
  Kleibacker, Fred R., 1916
  Klein, Frederic E., 1920
  Klein, Harriet J., 1907
  Kleinberger, F., 1915, 1916
  Kleppick, Ferd, 1901
  Kline, W.J.K., 1916
  Klipstein, A., 1912
- Klock - Knights (Box 49, Folder 12)
  Klock, Augustus, 1907
  Knauff, Theo. C., 1900
  Knauth, Nachod and Kühne (New York, N.Y.), 1904-1905
  Knibboff, [?],1899
  Knickerbocker Trust Co. Depositor's Committee [no place], 1908
  Kniffler, Oscar, 1901-1915
  Knight, Frank and Rutley (London, England), 1915
  Knight, H.J.J., 1903
  Knights of Columbus (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1917
  Knights of Pythias of Pennsylvania (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1915
  Knights Templar of Pennsylvania (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1906
- Knowland - Knox, Orville (Box 50, Folder 1)
  Knowland, Daniel P., 1913
  Knowles, Morris, 1919
  Knox and Reed (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1887-1900
  Knox, Hugh, 1913
  Knox, Orville M., 1919
- Knox, P.C., [1886?]-1919, undated (Box 50, Folder 2-7)
- Knox, Saml. - Kovacevic (Box 50, Folder 8)
  Knox, Saml. M., 1903-1906
  Kobbé, Gustav, 1909, 1915
  Koch, Joseph J., 1912
  Koerner, Harry G., 1907
  Kohler, Frank K., 1889
  Koles George W., 1917
  Konkle, Burton Alva, 1908, 1912
  Koonsen, W.F., 1911
  Koppel, Joseph, 1915
  Koradi, R., 1906
  Kough, Clark, 1915
  Kovacevic, Janko, 1906
- Knubel - Kuhman (Box 50, Folder 9)
  Knubel, Herman, 1909
  Kraushaar, C.W., 1913, 1915
  Krebs, Anna Frick Frantz, 1916
  Krebs, Stanley L., 1903-1904
  Kreisler, Fritz, 1920
  Kreps, J.W., 1905
  Kriehn, George, 1915